Hello everyone! This is Haruka Koizumi, aka Oharu.
Yes, that's right, look everyone! I am wearing a yukata!
Yes, I'm wearing a yukata, and the entire yukata coordination was produced by Jjolka,
This time, I asked Jiolka to do everything from the dressing to the hair and makeup.
So, today's project is about this yukata coordination. I asked for everyone's memories of one summer.
I asked for everyone's memories of summer, and I'm going to share them with you here.
I'd like to introduce them to you in this summery summer outfit. Let's go! Let's go!
Yes, I mean, does it look good on me? Is it a yukata?
I always wear my own pink yukata in the special selection activities.
I thought I would wear a blue or purple yukata, which is something I don't usually wear.
I decided to wear a blue or purple yukata, which is something I don't usually wear.
I also bought hair ornaments to go with it.
I bought all these hair ornaments at the scene.
I got all these hair ornaments for the scene.
I'm wearing a yukata by Grail.
Okay, I'd like to introduce them now.
How many did you wear this time?
Oh, I wore about 2,700.
Thank you.
Speaking of summer, fireworks
Yes, fireworks.
I like sparklers.
I'm scared of regular fireworks.
I'm also scared of fireworks.
I like sparkling fireworks.
Okay, I'd like to introduce some of my memories.
When I was in junior high school, girls came to the boys' dormitory to play cards and tell scary stories at the track team's camp.
Wow, that's great!
Was there any summer camp here? I don't think so.
My memories of junior high school are...
I didn't wear yukatas or anything like that.
But the gymnastic festival left a strong impression on me.
I remember that I left my hachimaki at home and had to go home to get it.
I also remember the centipede race that we all had together.
I think I have a strong memory of the P.E. festival.
The incident of leaving the freezer open.The case of the freezer left open.
That's a no-no.
That's, you know, even I wouldn't do that.
I know I'd get angry.
The time I went to a summer festival and bumped into my boyfriend and went home holding hands.
Here we are... memories like this... memories of a summer...
My summer memory will be visiting Niigata Park, thank you very much.
The fireworks festival in Atami...
I want to go to the fireworks show in Atami... it's absolutely beautiful.
I'm glad I got to see it with the final fireworks promotion department two years ago.
I'm glad we got to see the final fireworks two years ago.
I've never seen fireworks with the advertising team before.
So I was really happy to see them.
When I was in high school... we were all in uniform at the beach.
I was so happy to see them.
Wow, that's great... fireworks in school uniform is so much fun!
We usually go to Yamanashi Prefecture every summer and have fireworks at a campground in Yamanashi Prefecture.
But...
I'd like to go back to Yamanashi for barbecues and fireworks.
I really don't have any other plans this summer except for Tokisen. Thank you! I'm so glad! Let's have a fun summer! This year, I am scheduled to perform at Summer Stage, and I am also scheduled to perform on stage,
It will be the first time for me to perform on stage in the summer since the opener, so I am looking forward to having fun with you.
Please come and see me.
I teased him with a sideways glance as the sunflowers disappeared into the crowd.
Do you know what the lyrics are? Here are the lyrics to July Cider!
I teased the sunflowers that were disappearing in the crowd with my sideways glance
I did it a cappella!
Barbecuing and drinking from noon on, fireworks at night
I loved summers spent being a college student.
Oh, that's so cool!
Barbecues and handheld fireworks at night. College kids.
I'm welcoming all of them.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm always the one who eats and is told to grill, but I never get to be the one who cooks.
I'm always asked to be the griller, but I never get to be the eater.
But there's one thing I've been thinking about, and it's the same with cooking, too... I'm always told off for not grilling, but when I try, I'm told, "Oh, don't do it,
But when I try to cook something, they tell me, "Oh, don't do that. It's dangerous. Isn't that wrong? I think that's wrong.What? They tell me not to do it. It's dangerous. Isn't that wrong? I think.
Hmmm... What are you talking about? My summer memories are of cottage camping with a group of good friends, playing wargames all night long.
That's a great memory. That's what summer memories are all about.
I think I'm really weak at wargames.
I'm talking about something else... going on a yukata date with Oharu.
I want to go on a yukata date with everyone.
I'd like to go to a fireworks display or something like that and buy yakisoba or something like that.
You buy at the stall, buy from the food stalls, eat, and then go to the fireworks show. I'd like to watch the fireworks with them. It's nice, it's nice.
Ebichu-san's beach, where we go every year. Toki-Sen is also very much looking forward to going to Yamanakako.
Well, yes, I want to go there every year, but I can't,
I look forward to seeing EBITCHU's beach and orca, orca-sama, and so on every year,
I think, "Oh, I want to go, this is the year! I want to go there this year, but I can't go every year, so I hope to go there someday.
I'd like to go someday.
I've been watching a lot of live videos of the Famien concert.
I see footage of past Famien performances with a lot of water pouring out of them.
I think it looks really, really fun!
I went to my first live concert last summer. I'm glad I went. They are so cute!
Thank you.
That's right.
I remember going to my grandma's house and watching the local fireworks.
I've always wanted to go to a fireworks show with Kishen-chan.
I wonder where her grandma's house is.
I'm jealous of you... but your grandma's house is really close to mine.
So I don't often go far away to see my grandma.
I long to go back to my parents' house.
I just came back from a school trip to Okinawa.
Wow! That's nice! I'm jealous! Okinawa!
I went to Okinawa for a photo book.
It's been a while since I've been to Okinawa and it was a lot of fun.
I want to go to Okinawa again for my private time.
For the photo book, you shot in a villa-like place, right?
Yes, so there was a swimming pool, so I could swim as much as I wanted.
You know, like you can swim all you want in an open-air bath in a Japanese inn or something.
There was a pool like that.
Yes, it was so much fun that I wanted to go here privately.
I would like to go to Okinawa again, either for filming or for private use.I would like to go back to Okinawa again, either for filming or for private use.
But this summer I can go to Indonesia.
I'm really looking forward to Indonesia, too.
I'm looking forward to going to Indonesia this summer.
I'm looking forward to going to Indonesia with my colleagues and their families.
I'm sorry.
I remember when I was 18, I went to a fireworks display with my first boyfriend, who was older than me.
It's probably the most youthful thing I've ever done.
A fireworks display in a yukata.
What is it with men's yukata? Jimbaek? It's so nice, isn't it?
I like men in yukata. Girls wear furisode (long-sleeved kimono) and yukata, of course, and Japanese clothes give a totally different impression,
I think this outfit probably gives a totally different impression than usual, but I also like men in yukata in spring. I guess high school baseball? If it were now, I would have definitely chosen a cheering song or a time selection song.
Oh, I see, thank you. I'm glad it's a baseball cheer song or something.
I'm going to a fireworks display with someone I like this year. I'm going to confess my feelings there.
Good luck!
I want to make a lot of sweet and sour memories in the summer.
It was fun to go to Okinawa in the height of summer and do scuba diving in front of the mountain.
I saw a manta ray.
Oh, you can see these!
That's amazing!
I didn't know that.
I didn't know you could see manta rays in Okinawa.
Well, of course, there is the ocean.
I want to go there. Of course, they have the ocean. I want to go there. I want to go there. In Okinawa.
The Chulamee? Chulamee Aquarium? I want to go there so much.
When I was in high school, I had a lot of free time off from club activities. I had vacations. I only had Obon vacation.
Oh, I see. That's too bad. But Tokiseng was like that too.
Yes, I had a lot of lessons all the time.
Getting soaked at the festival. It was really fun.
It was fun, wasn't it? I had so much fun too.
I remember the first time I went to see Oharu-chan in the summer.
Thank you! I'm so glad you made the trip.
I'm going again this year. Let's have fun together.
I bravely invited the person I've had a crush on for 5 years to have dinner with me after the crossing.
It didn't taste good.
He's so cute!He's cute.
I wonder if they stop tasting before they confess or something.
He's cute.
When I first started golfing, I worked part-time at a golf course and played rounds after work.
I heard golf is really fun. I've seen it on YouTube.
I'm a little interested in it.
I see.
It's hard.
Do you think you can do it?
I went camping with friends on Tanabata night and went stargazing.
Today's the Tanabata.
It's Tanabata.
[Applause]
No, seriously.
I didn't realize it until I just read this.
It's Tanabata today.
Isn't it amazing that we're shooting this on Tanabata?
I can do it! I'm so excited!
I got my license and went on a trip to Hokkaido and drove.
I had to take a break from driving in high school so the last summer competition of my junior year is a memory I'll never forget.
It's great if you're a member of an athletic club or something.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who belong to an athletic club who say that their most memorable experience was their last competition.
When I see the sea in summer, I remember getting stung by a jellyfish.
Oh, you got stung by a jellyfish? Does it hurt?
I've heard so many stories about jellyfish.
I hear so many stories about jellyfish.
At least once a summer, I'm sure.
The fireworks over the Kamogawa River in Chiba with my daughter were amazing!
What? Let's check out some fireworks on the water!
Chiba... fireworks on the water... fireworks...
Wow! Wow!
Wow! That's amazing! I want to go so badly!
Well, I haven't been to a fireworks show since I was an adult.
Yeah, that's why I want to go.
Yeah, like a festival.
You know, people go on trips to places like Okinawa, and they come home from a fireworks display that reflects on the water, and they have a handheld fireworks display.I see you guys are traveling to Okinawa or something...coming home from an amazing fireworks display on the water and having a handheld fireworks show!
Looks like fun in front of Hana-hayamama!
I went to the beach with my childhood friend's family.
I love the ocean, don't you?
I haven't been to the beach since last year or the year before.
I've loved the ocean since the year before last and I couldn't even swim.
I used to be bad at it because I couldn't swim and the ocean was too salty, but after I started going with my friends, I started to like the ocean.
I went to the beach with my friends and I started to like the ocean.
I went to a training camp for my club's activities and worked hard for 4 days in the heat with my friends. I'm going again this year.
I'm going again this year. Good luck!
I want to do some kind of training camp again.
Watermelon splitting and fireworks with everyone. Sounds great! Watermelon splitting sounds fun! I don't think I can do it at all!
I went fishing with the boys during summer vacation, and we caught two bluefin squid.
Catching squid is amazing!
I love fishing!
Speaking of memories of summer, thanks for the most fun summer with my idols!
This year is something of a summer summer, or rather, a tour. We have until 9, so we have the tour and also, as I announced earlier,
I'm Haruka Kojima, and I'm going to be in a play called "Hikaru Genji-kun" at the Mitsukoshi Theater in Tokyo from August 12th. Kougenji-kun at the Mitsukoshi Theater in Tokyo from August 12,
I hope to spend an enjoyable summer with you all, and of course, there will be various live events such as Indonesia and Samaste.
So let's make the best summer together!
So, thank you all again for sending me this message.
Please follow us on Instagram as well.
See you again in the next video!
Bye-bye!
Let's make the best summer ever!